All the stories from the streets, they make their way out to your window.
Reawaken certain memories
This way you relive them again and again
One will change into the other
Until you don't know what is real
and it's true you've gone full circle it is not the first time you've been here
first set shooting today with Vince Voltage and it's like a pinup burger fry
scurly thing I love it we have makeup artists on set I'm going to link everyone
one down but it's a fun day and now we have like 12,000 more sets we want to do
so let's just move on
I'm Addie Graffe, I'm a giraffe
Giraffe? Giraffe? Giraffe?
It's called giraffe in English
Giraffe? Giraffe?
We'll go this way, we'll go that way
Who's gonna stop you?
Well it's true, you have been faking
Whatever it took you to get ahead
And the people you wish to remove yourself from
Where you sometimes try to demonstrate
Now it's all for no good reason
Except you just keep passing on
All the stories from the streets
You ain't got no idea where they come from
Fall back on a wave of life
And well, it burns and it turns
It breaks and burns
It all happens once again
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
It's really hard to prepare the next sets.
As always.
After I don't know how many sets and hours and hours of shooting, we're done!
It was so much fun!
I don't know when I had this crazy makeup on for the last time for a shoot, so I'm so
looking forward to the pictures.
Thanks to the whole team, this was a really great day.
Now it's time to drive home!
I told you, but I'm seeking...